topic: Ruby gems
deck: All::CS::Languages::Ruby::Gems
uid_tag: cs/languages/ruby/gems
notes:
-       uuid: 8cca1a5f-2cca-4780-8893-51fc4f1bfd42
        guid: km@+Hn){<@
        front: Code duplication detector
        back: '`flay`'
        include_reverse: true
-       uuid: d679de6e-d843-4a77-ad14-7995d40af3e9
        guid: Eg)z7~0xGA
        front: Fuzz tester
        back: '`heckle`'
        include_reverse: true
-       uuid: a2a940d3-2599-4a6c-87f0-aea0fd6d7c2c
        guid: s}t&4v:7^!
        front: Code complexity estimator
        back: '`flog`'
-       uuid: f613302b-0f8f-46bd-ba74-605cd2502ce2
        guid: y-TWR_An9o
        front: English stemmer
        back: '`fast-stemmer`'
-       uuid: ccd58834-8054-4bb3-b9c3-b83f9b5f6e5f
        guid: s6WA7IgC;~
        back: Web automation
        front: '`mechanize`'
        include_reverse: true
-       uuid: f5ebb7a0-8375-4c08-ac28-e17b0850bf4c
        guid: y5@l/l*]9r
        front: '`capybara`'
        back: Web integration/acceptance tester
        include_reverse: true
-       uuid: 47ab2974-b46e-4c9d-964a-57043424c9ea
        guid: f]y?s@*v%5
        front: '`highline`'
        back: CLI interface builder
        include_reverse: true
-       uuid: 46dc8cbb-5390-4646-b36f-89d29bca1a40
        guid: K-}SXzibjS
        front: Pretty-printer gems
        back: '`pp`, `ap`'
        include_reverse: true
-       uuid: 5a031d14-0c09-40f1-b888-ba65561ef6b0
        guid: IRFMU%p7YP
        front: '`grit`'
        back: Git library
        include_reverse: true
-       uuid: 5e9eb8b2-680f-41e4-858a-6f38c628d8cb
        guid: P0lS0tC7y@
        front: '`ribbit`'
        back: libgit2 bindings library
        include_reverse: true
-       uuid: 969336d7-201f-455e-a278-5cf3134cc37e
        guid: zDx4d68V`8
        front: '`rspec`'
        back: Spec-driven testing
        include_reverse: true
-       uuid: 6eb74385-2d5e-441d-8591-994194033363
        guid: A2`FC/[OSB
        front: '`better_errors`'
        back: Better error screens for Rails
        include_reverse: true
-       uuid: f2a00d5d-68f7-4c19-8678-a730d16e8116
        guid: M*LUrD)Pn,
        front: '`conductor`'
        back: Web console for Rails
        include_reverse: true
-       uuid: c3f80d5d-eb97-4473-a1ec-034e01235446
        guid: g*}h/b+yF_
        front: '`bullet`'
        back: (N+1)-query killer
        include_reverse: true
-       uuid: 27727456-7392-42cb-a127-a637dbe88bd4
        guid: J;_38)NK^i
        front: '`faker`'
        back: Fake test data generator
        include_reverse: true
